## **Andrew Reyes**

E-mail: andrewjordanreyes@gmail.com

Phone: (360) 481-8868 // LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/andrew-reyes-05b262108/ GitHub: github.com/andrwjrdn // Portfolio: andrwjrdn.github.io/MainPortfolio/

### **PROFILE**

Dedicated web developer driven to learning the latest technologies. Passionate in creating a friendly and interactive front-end/UI for users. Around 10 years of retail management, HR, and Education experience; Aspires to dive into the tech industry and contribute to the best of my abilities. A fast and motivated learner that strives in a team environment along with top notch communication skills makes me a great asset to any organization.

#### **TECHNOLOGIES**

HTML	CSS	Javascript	MongoDB	MS Office
MySQL	React.js	Express.js	Handlebars.js	Firebase
Node.js	jQuery	Java	Python	AJAX

# **PROJECTS**

<rendezvous/>

Technologies: MERN STACK, Redux, Material UI

Summary: A meet-up app for developers to coordinate events. Responsible for front-end and UI.

GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/andrwjrdn/Code-Meetup">https://github.com/andrwjrdn/Code-Meetup</a>

**Plateful** 

Technologies: HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, Node, Express, Sequelize, Handlebars

Summary: A recipe application which users enter in ingredients they have at home and our API will

display recipes to the user. Responsible for back-end routing.

GitHub: https://github.com/andrwirdn/Project2

**IDBUG** 

Technologies: HTML, CSS, Javascript, AJAX, ¡Query, Firebase

**Summary:** IDBug is a fast way for our users to identify a possible diagnosis for their symptoms and find a doctor near by. User's are also be able to login so they can view their search history. Responsible for

front-end/UI.

GitHub: https://github.com/andrwjrdn/Project-1

**Pokemon Game** 

Technologies: Python, PyGame

**Summary:** A game where you must defeat the evil Mewtwo! **GitHub:** <a href="https://github.com/andrwjrdn/PokemonPython">https://github.com/andrwjrdn/PokemonPython</a>

**EDUCATION** 

University of Washington - Seattle, WA (Feb. 2019 - Aug. 2019)

Full Stack Development Coding Certificate

Washington State University - Pullman, WA (Aug. 2013 - Aug. 2015)

B.A. - Human Development/Psychology

**EXPERIENCE** 

Issaquah School District (Jul. 2017 - Apr. 2019)

BASC Asst. Site Coordinator

• Responsible for the overall management of all before and after school facilities, staff, and students. Built a strong community between the school and families.

#### **Pacific Market Research**

(May 2016 - May 2017)

**HR** Assistant

• Utilized multiple HR systems as well as hired/trained/managed over 100 employees. Responsible for boosting monthly progress for 4 consecutive months by implementing new weekly progress.